

## **Andrea Garcia**

Nationality: Colombian Date of birth: 30/12/1991 Gender: Female

Phone number: (+356) 99977911 Email address: ing.camilagarcia@outlook.com

**Website:** <a href="https://github.com/milaca1991">https://github.com/milaca1991</a>

• Home: Santorini apartament 5 Trig Don Mawru Inguanez, Birkirkara, BKR4813, BIRK IRKARA, BKR 1250 Birkirkara (Malta)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I have experience as a Sales Representative and consultant, identifying a customer's needs, offering products or services, and ensuring they have a positive experience. As a strategic planner, implementing strategies and managing projects, organized and led teams.

Also, I have a passion for web development and am currently improving my skills through courses and personal projects. Am proficient in front-end languages such as JavaScript, HTML, and CSS(SCSS), as well as frameworks like React. This allows me to develop modern and visually appealing web solutions.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Strategic business planning manager

**Electroequipos** [ 06/2021 - 02/2023 ]

City: BOGOTA
Country: Colombia

Design and implementation of long-term business strategies and their monitoring. Leadership in the execution and tracking of key projects, ensuring their completion. Creation of advanced data visualization solutions with Power BI for strategic decision making. Planning for the implementation of new technology projects.

### Sales representative

**Parnasse Cosmeticos** [ 01/2018 – 01/2019 ]

City: BOGOTA
Country: Colombia

Offer and promote products to distributors in stores such as beauty salons, natural stores, and drugstores. Establish business relationships with distributors ensuring that the products are presented and offered properly. Keep contact with customers, especially those who need to replenish their stock

### **Consultant**

Levin global [ 02/2015 - 10/2017 ]

City: BOGOTA
Country: Colombia

Responsible for client management, billing and ensuring customer satisfaction throughout the project lifecycle. Leadership skills in managing and motivating project teams, and expertise in customer service and proposal development, and client acquisition.

## **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

Certified Tech Developer, Computer Programming *Digital House* [ 2022 – Current ]

**Business Intelligence Project Management Specialist** 

Politécnico Grancolombiano [ 2015 – 2016 ]

Address: BOGOTA

**Industrial Engineering** 

Politécnico Grancolombiano [ 2008 - 2013 ]

Address: BOGOTA